接下来，我们将检查文件夹是否存在。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Next, we're going to
check whether or not the folder exists.
因此，我将包括另一个系统库，fs 和
So I'm going to include another
system library, fs, and
我们把那个拿出来。
we will just grab that out.
因此，path 和 fs 都构建在节点中。
So both path and fs are built in the node.
我们不需要安装这些。
We don't have to install those.
所以我可以说如果，如果这不是真的，我们就否定它。
So then I can say if, and
we're gonna negate this if it's not true.
所以如果它不存在，我们要使用同步
So if it doesn't exist and
we're gonna use sync so
我们，我们不必做链接，我们会说，如果目录不存在,
we that we don't have to do chaining and
we'll say if the directory doesn't exist,
我们需要创造它。
we need to create it.
但是我们有一个问题，那就是，我又做了一次，这是出口，而不是出口。
But we have a problem here, which is that,
I did this again, it's exports not export.
今天把我的案子搞混了。
Got my cases confused today.
如果它不存在，我们需要创造它，但是问题是
If this doesn't exist,
we need to create it, but the problem with
默认的 make directory 命令是一次只执行一个级别。
the default make directory command is
that it will only do one level at a time.
没有什么能阻止人们说他们想要他们的内容
And there is nothing stopping somebody
from saying that they want their content
目录为源内容文档，这将是三个目录，将
directory to be source content docs, and
that would be three directories that would
需要创建，这将阻塞标准 mkdir 命令。
need to be created which would
choke the standard mkdir command.
所以我们要使用一个库来简化这个过程，这个叫做 mkdir p 或
So we're gonna use a library to make this
simpler, and this is called mkdir p or
我在脑海中说的方式是 mkdirp，所以我们要去纱线工作区
the way that I say it in my head is
mkdirp so we're going to yarn workspace
盖茨比-主题文档添加 mkdirp。
gatsby-theme-docs add mkdirp.
如果我能拼出来，mkdirp。
If I can spell it, mkdirp.
这样我们就可以
This will allow us to actually
递归地创建目录。
create directories recursively.
所以我们要导入它。
So we're gonna import that.
如果目录不存在,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
if the directory doesn't exist,
我们会创造它。
we will create it.
因此，我们将运行同步。
So we will run sync.
我们再次强调，我们只是想确保这些事情在它继续发展之前发生
Again, we're just trying to make sure that
these things happen before it moves on
空气污染指数的下一部分。
to the next part of the API.
这就是为什么我们使用同步模式。
That's why we're using
the synchronous mode.
这些手术应该会很快。
And these operations
should be pretty quick.
所以就性能成本而言，它可以忽略不计。
So in terms of performance
cost it's gonna be negligible.
那么，这应该行得通。
That then, should work.
所以，让我们继续前进，跑我们的开始。
So let's go ahead and run our start.
我们可以在主题 dev 中看到，我们没有文档文件夹。
And we'll see over here in the theme dev,
we do not have a docs folder.
所以如果我们做对了，接下来会发生什么呢
So if we did this right,
what will happen is I'm gonna start
主题开发网站在开发模式，我们将看到文档文件夹弹出。
the theme dev site in develop mode, and
we will see that docs folder pop up.
让我们继续这样做。
Let's go ahead and do that.
我们将运行纱线工作空间主题开发，和
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: We'll run yarn
workspace theme-dev develop, and
我们应该看到医生出现了，就是这样。
we should see docs pop up,
and there it is.
所以现在，如果我们尝试访问这个目录,
So now,
if we try to access that directory,
如果我们使用盖茨比源代码文件系统，我们马上就会到达
if we use the gatsby source filesystem
which we're gonna get to in a second, then
这将防止我们得到一个错误，内容路径无法找到。
that will prevent us from getting an error
that the content path can't be found.
所以这是一个很好的承诺点。
So that's a good point to commit.
让我们看看我们的进度。
Let's just check our progress here.
我们修改了 JSON 包，因为我们安装了 mkdirp,
We have modified the package JSON
because we installed mkdirp,
写了我们的 onprebootstrapping，我们写了实用程序文件夹。
wrote our onprebootstrapping,
we wrote that utility folder.
让我们把这些加起来
Let's just add all of that and
我们会得到提交和说主题开发,
we'll get commit and say theme-dev,
加上自举的东西。
add onprebootstrap stuff.